How serious were you two'?
(Raj:)Well, to be honest,
(Raj:)we only went on four dates,
hugged twice, kissed once,
(Raj:)and there was a handshake
loaded with sexual innuendo.
Wait, a girl you never slept with
sent you an email
(Emily:)and you felt so guilty about it
that you had to tell me?
(Penny:)Yeah.
(Emily:)That's kind of adorable.
(Raj:)Are you sure?
Because this is the part of the night
(Raj:)where I've said something stupid
and the girl usually leaves.
(Emily:)I'm still here.
(Raj:)Yeah, but now you make me wonder
what's wrong with you.
(Emily:)We just met.
(Emily:)You don't need to tell me about
other people you're seeing.
(Raj:)Really?
Because "I'm dating two women"
(Raj:)is basically the only cool thing
I can say about myself.